<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Esteban Suárez Barbán on Cubanoticias</title>
    <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/authors/esteban-su%C3%A1rez-barb%C3%A1n/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Esteban Suárez Barbán on Cubanoticias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Cubanoticias todos los derechos reservados</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:40:35 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/authors/esteban-su%C3%A1rez-barb%C3%A1n/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Femicide in Santiago de Cuba.</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/feminicidio-en-stgo-de-cuba-15122021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:40:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/feminicidio-en-stgo-de-cuba-15122021/</guid>
      <description>El asesino de Rosangela Vargas Noaya viajó de Matanzas a Santiago de Cuba para acabar con su vida y dejó huérfana a una menor de ocho años. (Foto: Mujeres Esperanza SC-Twitter)   Rosangela Vargas Noaya is the name of another victim of gender violence in Cuba. The 24-year-old woman was stabbed by her ex-partner in the Los Hoyos neighborhood, Santiago de Cuba province, on December 6.
The young woman, who was pregnant, also left an eight-year-old daughter who must suffer the loss of her and continue to grow in a society that has normalized attacks of this type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubanoticias.crypto your Unstoppable News Blockchain Website</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cubanoticias-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:32:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cubanoticias-crypto/</guid>
      <description>cubanoticias.crypto   The use of new technologies has raised new forms of struggle against the Cuban Communist Dictatorship. It spreads like a cancer throughout the democratic countries of the world.
Platforms such as blogger, twitter, facebook, youtube and other social networks have become ideological battlefields in which communists try to penetrate societies while subverting their order. The documented penetration of Cuban intelligence organizations in the countries of the region and in the educational centers of the world make it necessary to denounce by all possible means the danger that communism represents for the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
