<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Santiago de Cuba on Cubanoticias</title>
    <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/tags/santiago-de-cuba/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Santiago de Cuba on Cubanoticias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Cubanoticias todos los derechos reservados</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/tags/santiago-de-cuba/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fire destroys nine houses in Santiago de Cuba</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-stgo-de-cuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-stgo-de-cuba/</guid>
      <description>Alrededor de 25 personas perdieron todas sus pertenencias en el incendio ocurrido este jueves en Santiago de Cuba. (Foto: ACN)   Nine houses located on San Carlos Street, near Céspedes Park, in Santiago de Cuba, were destroyed by flames during a fire this Thursday morning.
At first, the local newspaper Sierra Maestra reported that five homes had been affected, but the Cuban News Agency (ACN) raised the figure to &amp;ldquo;nine rooms in a citadel&amp;rdquo;, thereby trying to reduce the magnitude of a disaster that left several families with nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Femicide in Santiago de Cuba.</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/feminicidio-en-stgo-de-cuba-15122021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:40:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/feminicidio-en-stgo-de-cuba-15122021/</guid>
      <description>El asesino de Rosangela Vargas Noaya viajó de Matanzas a Santiago de Cuba para acabar con su vida y dejó huérfana a una menor de ocho años. (Foto: Mujeres Esperanza SC-Twitter)   Rosangela Vargas Noaya is the name of another victim of gender violence in Cuba. The 24-year-old woman was stabbed by her ex-partner in the Los Hoyos neighborhood, Santiago de Cuba province, on December 6.
The young woman, who was pregnant, also left an eight-year-old daughter who must suffer the loss of her and continue to grow in a society that has normalized attacks of this type.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
