<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cubanoticias</title>
    <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cubanoticias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Cubanoticias todos los derechos reservados</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 08:53:35 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Los Mambises, a civic movement to boycott Cuban government businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/los-mambises-mov-cubano/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 08:53:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/los-mambises-mov-cubano/</guid>
      <description>Los Mambises is the name of a peaceful civic struggle movement, created this December with the purpose of boycotting the Cuban government&amp;rsquo;s businesses from social networks.
Its founder is Cuban activist based in Canada, Alberto Fonseca, who earlier this month protested, together with a friend, over the sale of Cubita coffee in stores in the city of Vancouver, a product associated with the state company CIMEX and the GAESA military conglomerate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire at ETECSA headquarters leaves eastern Cuba incommunicado</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-etecsa-17122021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-etecsa-17122021/</guid>
      <description>Groups of firefighters were mobilized to attend the fire that has caused a technological blackout. (Foto: Gretel Yanet-Facebook)   A fire broke out at the ETECSA headquarters in Las Tunas province on Thursday afternoon, leaving that Cuban territory completely incommunicado and partially affecting others.
According to the report by journalist Gretel Yanet, from the Provincial Radio Victoria Station, the incident at the territorial headquarters of the telecommunications monopoly in Cuba left that part of the eastern part of the country in a technological blackout, by paralyzing the internet service and mobile data, as well as radio and television signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire destroys nine houses in Santiago de Cuba</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-stgo-de-cuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-stgo-de-cuba/</guid>
      <description>Alrededor de 25 personas perdieron todas sus pertenencias en el incendio ocurrido este jueves en Santiago de Cuba. (Foto: ACN)   Nine houses located on San Carlos Street, near Céspedes Park, in Santiago de Cuba, were destroyed by flames during a fire this Thursday morning.
At first, the local newspaper Sierra Maestra reported that five homes had been affected, but the Cuban News Agency (ACN) raised the figure to &amp;ldquo;nine rooms in a citadel&amp;rdquo;, thereby trying to reduce the magnitude of a disaster that left several families with nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New collapse in Old Havana leaves at least one deceased</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/derrumbe-habana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/derrumbe-habana/</guid>
      <description>Según el periodista independiente Héctor Luis Valdés Cocho, vecinos del lugar afirman hay al menos cuatro fallecidos. (Collage: Vivian Delgado Barceló-Facebook)   This Thursday at least two people were injured in a collapse that occurred in Old Havana, as confirmed by the Provincial Government of People&amp;rsquo;s Power of the Cuban capital.
At 9:10 p.m. A wall of a building located on Angeles Street, Monte corner, in the Jesús María Popular Council collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion for sentencing the trial of the Cuban regime against Luis Robles</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/sentencia-luis-robles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/sentencia-luis-robles/</guid>
      <description>Luis Robles   The trial of Cuban political prisoner Luis Robles, held on Thursday in Havana, was concluded for sentencing, according to DIARIO DE CUBA. The Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office requests a joint penalty of six years in prison for the alleged crimes of &amp;ldquo;enemy propaganda and resistance.&amp;rdquo;
At the end of the hearing, the mother of the young man imprisoned for more than a year did not want to speak to the press, as she was very overwhelmed and crying when leaving the Municipal People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Marianao, as our journalist was able to verify on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban political prisoner Andy García, punished with two months without phone calls</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/andy-garcia-castigo-2meses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/andy-garcia-castigo-2meses/</guid>
      <description>Andy Garcia, Preso político cubanos   Cuban political prisoner Andy García Lorenzo has been punished with two months without telephone communication and threatened by the political police with adding one more charge to his file if he continues to collaborate with an initiative of his family to help other detainees with food after the historic protests July 11.
&amp;ldquo;The last thing we have is that they sanctioned my brother Andy Dunier García Lorenzo to two months without phone calls for giving me information about prisoners for us, through the project &amp;lsquo;Help the Brave of 11J&amp;rsquo; to help them with the bags&amp;rdquo; said Roxana García Lorenzo, the detainee&amp;rsquo;s sister, in a press group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Rick Scott demands from the White House actions in favor of Ferrer and other political prisoners</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/libertad-ferrer-rick-scott/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:23:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/libertad-ferrer-rick-scott/</guid>
      <description>Senadores Republicanos   MIAMI, United States. - Senator Rick Scott (R-F) demanded this Wednesday humanitarian attention for the Cuban opponent José Daniel Ferrer, held for several months in a jail in Santiago de Cuba, and for the hundreds of political prisoners on the island.
In telephone conversations with Juan González, senior adviser to the US National Security Council for the Western Hemisphere; António Guterres, Secretary General of the United Nations (UN); and Luis Almagro, secretary general of the Organization of American States (OAS), the legislator emphasized the situation of Ferrer, with whose relatives he also held exchanges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban authorities change location of Luis Robles trial hours before its celebration</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cambian-sitio-de-juicio-luis-robles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:23:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cambian-sitio-de-juicio-luis-robles/</guid>
      <description>Luis Robles   Havana Cuba. - The trial of the prisoner of conscience Luis Robles Elizástegui, which several days ago was scheduled for the Provincial People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Havana (commonly known as the Hearing of Havana), was suddenly relocated to the Municipal People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Marianao, as reported this Wednesday Robles&amp;rsquo;s lawyer to Landy Fernández Elizástegui, the prisoner&amp;rsquo;s brother.
The process is scheduled for this Thursday, December 16 at 9:00 in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The question of Cubans this December: &#39;what will we eat and drink by the end of the year?&#39;</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/que-comeran-los-cubanos-fin-anno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:23:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/que-comeran-los-cubanos-fin-anno/</guid>
      <description>Cubanos en calle de la Habana(Diario de Cuba)   &amp;ldquo;Everything is very expensive. I left the airport and on Ocho Vías, I was hungry, I stopped to eat something, one of these boxes that used to sell between 25, 30 or 50 pesos &amp;hellip; Well, the boxes are now about 270 pesos, almost 300 and they are two tablespoons of congrí, a rotten sweet potato and a rotten meat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Femicide in Santiago de Cuba.</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/feminicidio-en-stgo-de-cuba-15122021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 17:40:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/feminicidio-en-stgo-de-cuba-15122021/</guid>
      <description>El asesino de Rosangela Vargas Noaya viajó de Matanzas a Santiago de Cuba para acabar con su vida y dejó huérfana a una menor de ocho años. (Foto: Mujeres Esperanza SC-Twitter)   Rosangela Vargas Noaya is the name of another victim of gender violence in Cuba. The 24-year-old woman was stabbed by her ex-partner in the Los Hoyos neighborhood, Santiago de Cuba province, on December 6.
The young woman, who was pregnant, also left an eight-year-old daughter who must suffer the loss of her and continue to grow in a society that has normalized attacks of this type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cubanoticias.crypto your Unstoppable News Blockchain Website</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cubanoticias-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 08:32:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cubanoticias-crypto/</guid>
      <description>cubanoticias.crypto   The use of new technologies has raised new forms of struggle against the Cuban Communist Dictatorship. It spreads like a cancer throughout the democratic countries of the world.
Platforms such as blogger, twitter, facebook, youtube and other social networks have become ideological battlefields in which communists try to penetrate societies while subverting their order. The documented penetration of Cuban intelligence organizations in the countries of the region and in the educational centers of the world make it necessary to denounce by all possible means the danger that communism represents for the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manuel de Jesús Rojas Miranda, Another Human Rights violation in Cuba.</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/manuel-de-jesus-violacion-ddhh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 08:32:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/manuel-de-jesus-violacion-ddhh/</guid>
      <description>Manuel de Jesús Rojas Miranda   It&amp;rsquo;s been six months since my cousin. Manuel de Jesús Rojas Miranda , was kidnapped by State Security.
Prior to this event, he had been given a year without detention, for the Crime of Pre-criminal Social Danger (an invention that only exists in Cuba, used by the Dictatorship, to remove those who are annoying ). When there were two months to comply with this arbitrary sanction, they decided to kidnap him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
