<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Violación de Derechos Humanos on Cubanoticias</title>
    <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/tags/violaci%C3%B3n-de-derechos-humanos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Violación de Derechos Humanos on Cubanoticias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Cubanoticias todos los derechos reservados</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/tags/violaci%C3%B3n-de-derechos-humanos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion for sentencing the trial of the Cuban regime against Luis Robles</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/sentencia-luis-robles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/sentencia-luis-robles/</guid>
      <description>Luis Robles   The trial of Cuban political prisoner Luis Robles, held on Thursday in Havana, was concluded for sentencing, according to DIARIO DE CUBA. The Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office requests a joint penalty of six years in prison for the alleged crimes of &amp;ldquo;enemy propaganda and resistance.&amp;rdquo;
At the end of the hearing, the mother of the young man imprisoned for more than a year did not want to speak to the press, as she was very overwhelmed and crying when leaving the Municipal People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Marianao, as our journalist was able to verify on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban political prisoner Andy García, punished with two months without phone calls</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/andy-garcia-castigo-2meses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/andy-garcia-castigo-2meses/</guid>
      <description>Andy Garcia, Preso político cubanos   Cuban political prisoner Andy García Lorenzo has been punished with two months without telephone communication and threatened by the political police with adding one more charge to his file if he continues to collaborate with an initiative of his family to help other detainees with food after the historic protests July 11.
&amp;ldquo;The last thing we have is that they sanctioned my brother Andy Dunier García Lorenzo to two months without phone calls for giving me information about prisoners for us, through the project &amp;lsquo;Help the Brave of 11J&amp;rsquo; to help them with the bags&amp;rdquo; said Roxana García Lorenzo, the detainee&amp;rsquo;s sister, in a press group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban authorities change location of Luis Robles trial hours before its celebration</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cambian-sitio-de-juicio-luis-robles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:23:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/cambian-sitio-de-juicio-luis-robles/</guid>
      <description>Luis Robles   Havana Cuba. - The trial of the prisoner of conscience Luis Robles Elizástegui, which several days ago was scheduled for the Provincial People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Havana (commonly known as the Hearing of Havana), was suddenly relocated to the Municipal People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Marianao, as reported this Wednesday Robles&amp;rsquo;s lawyer to Landy Fernández Elizástegui, the prisoner&amp;rsquo;s brother.
The process is scheduled for this Thursday, December 16 at 9:00 in the morning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manuel de Jesús Rojas Miranda, Another Human Rights violation in Cuba.</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/manuel-de-jesus-violacion-ddhh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 08:32:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/manuel-de-jesus-violacion-ddhh/</guid>
      <description>Manuel de Jesús Rojas Miranda   It&amp;rsquo;s been six months since my cousin. Manuel de Jesús Rojas Miranda , was kidnapped by State Security.
Prior to this event, he had been given a year without detention, for the Crime of Pre-criminal Social Danger (an invention that only exists in Cuba, used by the Dictatorship, to remove those who are annoying ). When there were two months to comply with this arbitrary sanction, they decided to kidnap him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
