<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DDC on Cubanoticias</title>
    <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/authors/ddc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DDC on Cubanoticias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Cubanoticias todos los derechos reservados</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/authors/ddc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fire at ETECSA headquarters leaves eastern Cuba incommunicado</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-etecsa-17122021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-etecsa-17122021/</guid>
      <description>Groups of firefighters were mobilized to attend the fire that has caused a technological blackout. (Foto: Gretel Yanet-Facebook)   A fire broke out at the ETECSA headquarters in Las Tunas province on Thursday afternoon, leaving that Cuban territory completely incommunicado and partially affecting others.
According to the report by journalist Gretel Yanet, from the Provincial Radio Victoria Station, the incident at the territorial headquarters of the telecommunications monopoly in Cuba left that part of the eastern part of the country in a technological blackout, by paralyzing the internet service and mobile data, as well as radio and television signals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire destroys nine houses in Santiago de Cuba</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-stgo-de-cuba/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/incendio-stgo-de-cuba/</guid>
      <description>Alrededor de 25 personas perdieron todas sus pertenencias en el incendio ocurrido este jueves en Santiago de Cuba. (Foto: ACN)   Nine houses located on San Carlos Street, near Céspedes Park, in Santiago de Cuba, were destroyed by flames during a fire this Thursday morning.
At first, the local newspaper Sierra Maestra reported that five homes had been affected, but the Cuban News Agency (ACN) raised the figure to &amp;ldquo;nine rooms in a citadel&amp;rdquo;, thereby trying to reduce the magnitude of a disaster that left several families with nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New collapse in Old Havana leaves at least one deceased</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/derrumbe-habana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 13:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/derrumbe-habana/</guid>
      <description>Según el periodista independiente Héctor Luis Valdés Cocho, vecinos del lugar afirman hay al menos cuatro fallecidos. (Collage: Vivian Delgado Barceló-Facebook)   This Thursday at least two people were injured in a collapse that occurred in Old Havana, as confirmed by the Provincial Government of People&amp;rsquo;s Power of the Cuban capital.
At 9:10 p.m. A wall of a building located on Angeles Street, Monte corner, in the Jesús María Popular Council collapsed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion for sentencing the trial of the Cuban regime against Luis Robles</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/sentencia-luis-robles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/sentencia-luis-robles/</guid>
      <description>Luis Robles   The trial of Cuban political prisoner Luis Robles, held on Thursday in Havana, was concluded for sentencing, according to DIARIO DE CUBA. The Prosecutor&amp;rsquo;s Office requests a joint penalty of six years in prison for the alleged crimes of &amp;ldquo;enemy propaganda and resistance.&amp;rdquo;
At the end of the hearing, the mother of the young man imprisoned for more than a year did not want to speak to the press, as she was very overwhelmed and crying when leaving the Municipal People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Marianao, as our journalist was able to verify on the spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cuban political prisoner Andy García, punished with two months without phone calls</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/andy-garcia-castigo-2meses/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 16:39:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/andy-garcia-castigo-2meses/</guid>
      <description>Andy Garcia, Preso político cubanos   Cuban political prisoner Andy García Lorenzo has been punished with two months without telephone communication and threatened by the political police with adding one more charge to his file if he continues to collaborate with an initiative of his family to help other detainees with food after the historic protests July 11.
&amp;ldquo;The last thing we have is that they sanctioned my brother Andy Dunier García Lorenzo to two months without phone calls for giving me information about prisoners for us, through the project &amp;lsquo;Help the Brave of 11J&amp;rsquo; to help them with the bags&amp;rdquo; said Roxana García Lorenzo, the detainee&amp;rsquo;s sister, in a press group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The question of Cubans this December: &#39;what will we eat and drink by the end of the year?&#39;</title>
      <link>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/que-comeran-los-cubanos-fin-anno/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 20:23:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cubanoticias.info/en/posts/que-comeran-los-cubanos-fin-anno/</guid>
      <description>Cubanos en calle de la Habana(Diario de Cuba)   &amp;ldquo;Everything is very expensive. I left the airport and on Ocho Vías, I was hungry, I stopped to eat something, one of these boxes that used to sell between 25, 30 or 50 pesos &amp;hellip; Well, the boxes are now about 270 pesos, almost 300 and they are two tablespoons of congrí, a rotten sweet potato and a rotten meat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
